const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Who are the Bogdanoffs?',
      answers: ["The Alpha", "The Omega",
        "The puppetmasters",
        "French twin brothers who are television presenters"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'French twin brothers who are television presenters',
    },
    {
        question: 'Why are the Bogs famous?',
        answers: ["They're the ringleaders of a central cabal, which controls all of the world's monetary supply.",
        "They look unusual.",
        "They are the architects of the matrix we currently inhabit",
        "They are intraterrestrial time-travelers"],
        correctAnswer: "They look unusual.",
      },


      {
        question: 'What online community are the Bogdanoff twins most prominently associated with?',
        answers: ["Club Penguin",
            'My Little Pony imageboards',
            'Cryptocurrency',
            'Backpage'],
        correctAnswer: "Cryptocurrency",
      },

     {
         question:  "Dr. Bogdanoff & Dr. Bogdanoff are most renown in the scientific community for their accomplishments in...",
        answers: ["Publishing nonsensical theories",
            "Disproving the Theory of Relativity",
            "Zoology",
            "prosthetics"
        ],
        correctAnswer:"Publishing nonsensical theories" ,
        },

        {
        question:  "How many children do the Bogdanoff brothers have?",
        answers: ["We are all Bogs children.",
            "6",
            "9",
            "The answer is unfamthomable, mind boggling."
        ],
        correctAnswer:"6" ,
        },

        {
        question:  "What disorder is it theorized the twins suffer from?",
        answers: [ "Acromegaly",
            "Telepathy",
            "Greed",
            "Vainity",
        ],
        correctAnswer:"Acromegaly" ,
        },

        {
        question:  "The Bog boys were raised by...",
        answers: ["An AI sent from the future to divine its chosen followers",
            "Extraterrestrials",
            "Cory Baxter",
            "Countess Bertha Kolowrat-Krakowská" ],
        correctAnswer: "Countess Bertha Kolowrat-Krakowská",
        },

        {
        question:  "What is the Bogdanoff's one true weakness?",
        answers: ["Nobody",
            "No one",
            "Charles Norris",
            "Absolutely nothing, not even Chuck Norris"
        ],
        correctAnswer:"Absolutely nothing, not even Chuck Norris" ,
        },

        {
        question:  "Who would win in a fight, Igor Bogdanoff or Grichka Bogdanoff?",
        answers: ["They would both win, we would all lose.",
            "Igor",
            "Grichka",
            "Ron Paul"
        ],
        correctAnswer:"They would both win, we would all lose." ,
        },

        {
        question:  "How do the Bogdanoffs pronounce 'meme'?",
        answers: ["may may",
        "rhymes with dream",
        "rhymes with cream",
        "rhymes with Kanye's hit song 'Ultralight Beam'"
        ],
        correctAnswer:"may may" ,
        }
    ]